Now it is time for you to call
some tips for an online raffle
as a professional.
First tip,
focus on one raffle at a time.
This may be very obvious what I am saying,
but it is always better to lend
attention to one event than to several.
Also,
if you have several raffles at the same time,
you can make your own followers confused.
Second advice,
choose an award that is striking.
This will help more people sign up and make
other participants join the event.
Third board,
organizes test raffles to fine-tune details.
Checking this with your close circle,
you will be able to
to know which formats are most attractive to users,
what awards you can offer
and which process will be best suited
to what you want to achieve.
Fourth tip,
establishes the duration
and allocate the budget you will invest
to disseminate your dynamics.
Study your market,
analyzes the results of other similar dynamics
and sets out the goal of overcoming them.
5th tip,
measure results.
After the storm comes the calm.
the results you achieved,
for example,
the number of people who participated,
the comments there were,
the reaction to the awards you offer.
This will help you decide,
obviously,
whether you organize another raffle or not.
6th and final board,
you can get close to small influencers
to help you with the dissemination